Inventory of the Ernest Fred Easterbrook papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ernest Fred Easterbrook Papers, 1903-2006 (Boxes 1-22)
  - Diary transcriptions
    Also in the Easterbrook collection are two diaries covering the same period (early to mid-1944). One of those diaries, labeled "Supplemental Diary," seems to have been written when he had time to gather his thoughts and write in a more complete manner. Those entries are designated by a box drawn around them.
    Easterbrook originally drew the military unit symbols used in these diaries. The software used to reproduce the symbols uses a font from Tom Mouat's MapSymbs website (www.mapsymbs.com). The software is Mouat's intellectual property but can be copied freely. Tom was most gracious and generous with his time to ensure that the symbols worked properly.
    Easterbrook's son, John, transcribed the diaries into DOC files, converted them to PDFs, and transferred them to Hoover in 2011. Hoover digitized the maps in the diaries, creating JPG files, in 2011.
    - Volume 1, 1944
    - Volume 2, 1945